Summer vacation breezed right on by.
Time to start planning the culture festival.
Uh...
Following the lottery, your request to perform at this year's festival is denied.
Instead, Class 2-7's assignment will be food and drinks.
With their mission as clear as ice,
our frosty friends got to work!
By the way, did you and Tommy hit the library over the break?
Gah! Are you stalking us now?
Capacho spotted you.
That dude's got eyes everywhere!
Wait, really? The library date? That is so wholesome.
Well, it started as a library date, but then...
But then we read books! Just forget about it!
How did things go with you and that girl?
Huh?
We got each other's digits before the break, so what happened?
Yeah, give us the goss.
Uh...
I mean, she and I did text a little bit every now and again.
That's as far as things got for some reason.
That's weird.
I've ruined everything.
What?
We messaged back and forth for a while, but I never knew texting could be so hard!
I'd sit for hours trying to think of how to respond.
Done.
I'd write a paragraph, then Yamada would send me a one-word reply!
My message is supposed to be short. Am I doing this wrong?
I could write less, but I'm worried if I do that I'll just come off totally creepy and scare him away!
Why don't you just leave him on red?
No!
I mean, it's hard, but I don't think I don't like it.
But sometimes he tries calling me...
And I panic! I've turned him down twice now!
Oof. Ouch.
I got scared, and I lied, and I'm sure he's all through it!
And now he probably thinks I'm a horrible person who hates his guts!
That is bleak.
Now, hold up! She's still texting you!
You think she just prefers not to talk on the phone?
I mean, yeah, that could be, but...
I don't know, man. I suck at this.
Relax. Tell us some more about this girl.
Yeah, till now, I thought your type was goofball girls that match your goofball energy.
Same. You read my mind.
I guess that's kind of true, but...
Memory lane is waiting! Follow me!
When the giggles have a surprise source, Yamada's heart melts like a snowball!
Once upon a time.
So you probably already know this.
But I'm super into you, Yamada!
Oh!
Sweet! Let's date!
Yay!
Wee!
You know, even though Yamada's always been like this, he made it work with his ex for a good chunk of time.
I've always been like, what now?
And yeah, we did break up, but we're still friends.
Oh, you're so lucky.
Wish it went that way for me when I was young.
Girl, what? Why are you talking like an old raisin?
I'm low-key jelly, though. Folks who have legit dated have so much know-how and XP to help them,
while I'm still learning everything on the fly.
You and Tani are legit.
But he's basically my first boyfriend, so I'm just guess-handing my way through stuff.
Hey now, we don't tolerate Rihi erasure around here.
Rihi?
Don't touch your eyes
Check your eyes
Cast your camera
advance with the love
It's own love
I'm in a circle close to the open
Here is your​ prayer
To umvelness
Thank you.
心が体に追いついて 気付けば目で覆ってる
眼鏡を外してさ ちゃんと目を合わせてよ
恋は走り出しても 放課後まで待てない
大事な言葉ほど 酸素を切らみたい
辞書にない私なりの言葉で 早く 早く 早く 君に伝えなきゃね
わり 繁積する
フルヒーが見える
どう handle it
必要ですけど
うん
本棚內 Together's uniforms
We need supplies for the badges and plushie stands.
Right.
Huh?
Hey Hon, Tani is here.
The guy I told you about.
Who?
Oh, you mean the quiet glasses guy with the loud pink girlfriend.
Wait, I said that?
Let's go.
Grab whatever you want and we'll check out, okay?
They were looking right at us and clearly talking about us.
But why?
Is there anything you can't buy at this shop?
Rewind, who's Rihi?
Um, he's just... somebody.
The absolute disrespect.
Are you trying to say my boy doesn't count?
No, it was just an entirely different sitch, okay?
I was just a dumb baby kid making dumb baby kids...
Yo, check me out!
Giant menu boards now unlocked!
Whoa, those are sick!
Sick!
It's like they're from a real restaurant!
Wada!
Is that your handwriting, Sato?
And my art.
So pro!
Well, she's distracted.
Can you tell me what Rihi's like?
Oh.
Yeah, he's cool!
Oh...
Actually, he's coming to the festival, so you can meet him then.
Oh?
What should we do next, babe?
Uh, no, babe.
You wanna try that new dessert place?
Oh, gee!
Let's do it!
About Suzuki.
Is she your first girlfriend?
Yeah.
Not as much.
You ever feel like you're not cut out for dating?
Like you're screwed because you have no experience?
What a stupid question.
Of course he doesn't.
He's not that kind of guy.
And here I am asking him for advice when I used to look down on him.
How pathetic.
I do.
Really?
I'm not... confident.
I see.
We did it!
It's the first day of the festival.
Okay, team meat on three!
One, two, three!
Meat!
On day two, even the public can come chill.
Hold down the fort while my man and I rom-com it up.
So cringe.
We're all good.
Ciao!
Look at your shirt.
You're so popular.
Aw, I'll go.
Oh!
You still gotta write something.
Like what?
Something cutesy just for me.
Su-zu-ki, I look...
Don't read it out loud, you little freak.
And please don't read it silently either.
You still call your girlfriend by last name?
That's mad weird, bro.
That is weird.
Apparently all of you call me that too!
So, where do you want to go first?
Is there anything you missed out on last year?
Our class project was a play.
I didn't get to leave my home room.
What?!
Well, lucky for you, you've got the perfect guide to the perfect tour.
That sounds great.
First things first, we'll plan around the events happening at specific times.
If we get hungry, we can munch on snacks and chug tea in the PTA room.
And we gotta check out all the different class and club exhibits!
I have nothing to do.
People keep peeking inside and then leaving.
Even zero traffic!
I must be driving everyone away with how low-fitting I am!
Over here!
We haven't hit this one yet!
Oh!
It's them again!
I know!
That wasn't your thing!
Somehow this is even worse than strangers coming in here!
Oh no!
Oh no no no!
She must be saying, hey, don't you guys work at the library together?
And now they're going to try to talk to me!
Stay back!
We don't know each other!
No traffic!
I must be driving everyone away with how low-fitting I am!
Over here!
We haven't hit this one yet!
Oh no!
Oh no no no!
She must be saying, hey, don't you guys work at the library together?
And now they're going to try to talk to me!
Stay back!
We don't know each other!
I can't talk to you people!
Heya!
Sorry!
Do you care if we chat while we check out your neat pics?
Oh!
Uh, no, that'd be okay!
Whoa!
They really do look like a couple!
So when did the photographer come back?
Oh no!
So when does the photography club meet up?
I didn't know you meant chat with me!
Oh!
Um!
We don't really ever meet up for any, um, meet ups!
We just take photos on our own!
Ah!
The more you know!
Hey!
I think this one's my fave!
It's Toad's Gorge!
That was one that I took-
Dang!
Are you serious?
Work it, girly!
No!
It's really nothing special!
Aw!
Don't be so modest!
You've got talent!
Teach me your secrets, witch!
Where is the magic camera?
I don't have one of those!
The camera's actually meant for beginners!
Wow!
Which one's your favorite, Tawny?
That.
A cat?
I mean, sure, it's a good photo, but do you like it?
Or do you just like cats?
Right?
Thanks for the photo lesson, photo witch!
I can't believe it!
That was one of the smoothest conversations I've had!
There weren't any awkward silences unless I got to talk about a topic I like!
If only that could happen every single time!
Just speak coherently and don't let my nerves take over!
Stay put, I'll walk in your direction.
Maintain a cheerful and pleasant demeanor?
So, what's in front of you?
Positive energy!
I see a guy wearing a blue cap!
Oh!
I, um...
I haven't seen you in a while...
Hello?
Yamada?
You still there?
Uh...
Yeah, it is.
He was literally just here a minute ago.
Oh, man!
He left?
I wonder where he ran off to after he hung out.
Oh!
Hey!
Huh?
Is this Yamada's classroom?
Uh, yeah it is.
He was literally just here a minute ago.
Oh man, he left?
I wonder where he ran off to after he hung up on me.
No worries though, I'll find him eventually.
Thanks anyway!
What a babe.
Wait...
Is that guy...?
Oh yeah!
Hit the jackpot!
I squirt so much stuff it feels like highway robbery!
Hey, be careful where you're walking.
Oh, well, I'm not sure what he's going to do.
Oh, I'm not sure what he's going to do.
I'm not sure what he's going to do.
But wait, he's not sure what he's going to do.
Oh man, he left?
I wonder where he ran off to after he hung up on me.
No worries though, I'll find him eventually.
Thanks anyway!
What a babe.
wait is that guy oh yeah hit the jackpot i scored so much stuff it feels like highway robbery
hey be careful where you're walking oops hang on suzu game are you
whoa i thought that was you it's been a while
rihito huh oka hey sato long time no see you're here i am who's this guy a friend from middle school
hey tani this is rihito oka he and i went to middle school together did you come out here by yourself
nah i'm here with friends from my school i'm just operating solo for a minute i came to say hi to
yamata you and miyu since you're all in the same class thanks visiting you guys convenient
yeah but feels like it's been forever like how long now probably not since middle school right
so how's life oh life is lifing
god this is awkward
it's been so long my only option is to force a small and slog my way through small talk
get your butt over here yamata i need backup what was i thinking it's been long enough that i
figured i could just play it cool and act like nothing happened but it's totally backfiring
only things haven't gotten weird between us sure this is the hill you want to die on miyu
a sick beat makes a song that is a bona fide scientific fact thanks dj phd
you guys are always together when are you gonna start dating already
you know you want to man this is getting old why would we do that i don't know you just should
this is one of those situations where if we keep saying no they'll just keep pushing us harder
i'll go with the flow and let me you be the one to shut it down
what do you say you want to go out with me huh
wait like on a date uh wake-ups
come on i was totally joking
i guess what's done is done
we both started out thinking that dating a friend wasn't the worst thing in the world
but it's so awkward i can't even think of what kind of stuff we usually talk about
we used to crack jokes and make each other laugh but now that we're dating everything suddenly feels so serious
do you want to like try holding hands or something
it's not like i hate rito in some ways it's weird because i actually like him
no way
i don't have the words to explain why but this isn't right
i had a feeling dating really isn't us is it
don't we don't vibe like this let's just forget it we'll rewind
what do you say friends of course he'd say that
i didn't give him any other choice sorry
why the guiltier you feel for something that happened in the past
the harder it is to shake the yuck out of your heart
so
apologizing now would be way too selfish
i'd be doing it just to make myself feel less guilty about us
say miyu
whenever the old crew hangs
do you pass when you know i'll be there
that must suck you should get to come too
we're all good so don't worry okay
let's all hang out again soon we're friends after all
come on miyu seal the deal boom
uh boom
see ya i'm gonna look for yamada
and once again he only said that because i made things weird what is my deal
i thought you guys had already cleared the air
nah we're a disaster
but weirdly i think this kind of helped
i really do
it's like all the uneasiness i've been hanging on to just evaporated
maybe you feel better but what about the rest of us who had to sit and watch you two win gold in the awkward olympics
oh sorry
tell her tawny
just classmates
well we'll give you love birds some privacy
so anyway
he and i tried dating but it took us like two seconds to realize that was a terrible idea
now he knows
i told him the truth because i didn't want him thinking i had something to hide
was that a mistake
what happened happened but rihito's never been anything more than a friend to me i promise
fine
are you okay
poor tawny
maybe he wanted someone with a totally clean slate
i know this is super complicated but i think if he was my first for real boyfriend
i don't want you to have to coddle me
i'm sorry the problem is with me not you
i just need to clear my head okay
hey man i've been looking for you
yeah sorry about that
no sweat you gave me time to nip the weird miyu thing in the butt
what you two weren't getting along
not really you know how weird things got
totally bro
yeah we decided we're just gonna erase that chapter
bury it down deep
i still remember all my mistakes like they were yesterday
but i'm great
i've just decided i'm not gonna date anyone ever again
so i'll never give my friends a reason to hate me
what
how could anyone ever hate you rihi
yama
i just don't get it
what did he mean the problem is with him
he's probably just jealous
of what rihi do when i have negative vibes
well he is crazy hot
so he's just a dude who happens to be hot and happens to be my friend
i learned in middle school that even if a relationship checks the right boxes it can still mean nothing
but it didn't mean nothing
otherwise i wouldn't look back at it with so much guilt and regret
still though
you guys were each other's first partner
that is so pure and wholesome
i really miss the days when i was that innocent
that's super messed up
it doesn't matter if you've been with people
we've all got a past
acting like not having a history makes you more pure is messed up
are you okay
it's like a switch flipped
i could have slept with a hundred guys and it still wouldn't matter
whoa
i want to love tawny
and i want to be sincere and dedicated and true to him
is there anything purer than that
all right i'm off to find my man
uh
oh
slow runner
man
now i suddenly wish i was in love
sorry
oh
it's just you
what the hell
i always figured she'd have friends i didn't know about
her personality is magnetic
and it's pointless feeling bothered by what's happened in her past
but even so
let's all hang out again soon
i can't help worrying about what it means for us
and for our future
every day i'm with her
instead of getting confident
i'm getting greedy
it's like my heart is shrinking
tawny
i love you
i chose you
understand
you're not afraid to be who you are and you always say what you mean
i love that
but every now and then
you'll tell me you're fine even when your thoughts are running around in circles in your head like pesky little brain goblins
it's all right
even if your mind is cloudy or you're still processing something
i want you to know that if you ever feel anxious or on edge about anything
you can talk to me
attention the ward ceremony is about to start go to the gym announcement over
maybe we should just stay here like this
i know i shouldn't compare myself to others
but i couldn't help but get anxious earlier
i couldn't control my reaction and i hated myself for it
really so you weren't mad at me
no
i'm sorry for making you feel like that
don't be
is there anything else
honestly he seems more like your type than i do
what
don't open up that can of worms or else i gotta think about all the people who'd be better for you than me
there aren't any
don't lie
then who
well i don't know
what are we even talking about
miu
is that what they called you back then
oh no it wasn't like a thing that everybody did
murihito was the type to go against the grain when it came to that kind of stuff
murihito
hey tiny if there's something you want to say then spill it
no thanks it's fine
tiny
year two class seven
i really wanna
yusuke
tani
miu
suzuki
jim
now
i'm not doing this again
crap they noticed
it's time to head over
okay yusuke
man how did everyone get down there so fast
we're definitely gonna raise some eyebrows when we walk in late together
time to get our story straight
lock in yusuke
you don't have to call me that
yeah hey
hey
o決まりのフレーズは引き出しの中へ
何よりも振り切って声を出してみる
鏡の奥まで目を凝らして
Ah, ziggi ziggi na 道を抜け
居合わせた影も
曇る窓へ描くように
打ち取ってほしい
言葉で透き通ったり
縮む幻
差し込めた火を踏んで
跳ねた色も少しだけ好きになる
ねぇ 今を隠されちゃう前に
意外な魔法をかけ合って
わからなくて
わからないねって話して
絵が触った後に滲ってた匂いが
雨みたいに伝ってる